Rhianna Waddington

Housekeeping Supervisor - Clarion Hotel

Ridley Park, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Rhianna-Waddington/36f734eb36217c9d

Housekeeping Supervisor that is also a seasoned customer service specialist with background in providing advice on

diverse customer situations. Providing friendly customer service with a can-do attitude and willingness to help at all

times. Specializing in quality service, customer retention, productivity and team management. Work with fellow employees when needed to assist in having them complete their daily task.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Housekeeping Supervisor

Clarion Hotel - Essington, PA - July 2013 to Present

Assisted guests with any special requests during their visits. Cleaned rooms to the satisfaction of all clients. Stocked

room attendant carts with supplies. Replenished quest supplies and amenities.

Secretary

Noahs Ark Plumbing - Ridley Park, PA - January 2011 to July 2013

Provided accurate and appropriate information in response to customer inquiries. Scheduled appointments and filed

invoices.

Child Caregiver

Little Tykes Daycare - Springfield, PA - June 2009 to July 2013

Responsible for observing and monitoring children's activities at all times. Provided an optimal learning environment.

Always maintained the health and well-being of children under my care.

EDUCATION

Delaware County Community College - Media - Media, PA 2012

High School Diploma

Ridley High School - Folsom, PA 2009